[
  {
    "front": "Teacher",
    "back": "nauczyciel",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a teacher someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać nauczyciel.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Doctor",
    "back": "lekarz",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a doctor someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać lekarz.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Nurse",
    "back": "pielęgniarka",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a nurse someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać pielęgniarka.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Engineer",
    "back": "inżynier",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a engineer someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać inżynier.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Architect",
    "back": "architekt",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a architect someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać architekt.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Lawyer",
    "back": "prawnik",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a lawyer someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać prawnik.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Dentist",
    "back": "dentysta",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a dentist someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać dentysta.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Farmer",
    "back": "rolnik",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a farmer someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać rolnik.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Chef",
    "back": "szef kuchni",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a chef someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać szef kuchni.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Waiter/Waitress",
    "back": "kelner/kelnerka",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a waiter/waitress someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać kelner/kelnerka.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Builder",
    "back": "budowlaniec",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a builder someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać budowlaniec.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Artist",
    "back": "artysta",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a artist someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać artysta.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Actor/Actress",
    "back": "aktor/aktorka",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a actor/actress someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać aktor/aktorka.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Musician",
    "back": "muzyk",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a musician someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać muzyk.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Driver",
    "back": "kierowca",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a driver someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać kierowca.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Scientist",
    "back": "naukowiec",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a scientist someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać naukowiec.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Photographer",
    "back": "fotograf",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a photographer someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać fotograf.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Police officer",
    "back": "policjant",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a police officer someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać policjant.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Firefighter",
    "back": "strażak",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a firefighter someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać strażak.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Hairdresser",
    "back": "fryzjer",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a hairdresser someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać fryzjer.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Cleaner",
    "back": "sprzątaczka",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a cleaner someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać sprzątaczka.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Accountant",
    "back": "księgowy",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a accountant someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać księgowy.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Plumber",
    "back": "hydraulik",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a plumber someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać hydraulik.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Electrician",
    "back": "elektryk",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a electrician someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać elektryk.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Veterinarian",
    "back": "weterynarz",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a veterinarian someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać weterynarz.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Manager",
    "back": "menadżer",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a manager someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać menadżer.",
    "remembered": false
  },
  {
    "front": "Receptionist",
    "back": "recepcjonista",
    "phonetic": "",
    "frontExample": "I'd like to become a receptionist someday.",
    "backExample": "Chciałbym kiedyś zostać recepcjonista.",
    "remembered": false
  }
]